The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight,
and despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove that to the whole world,
and to become the next Wizard King.
In preparation for the coming war with the Spade Kingdom,
Asta and his comrades trained diligently
with the Heart Kingdom's spirit guardians.
Now halfway into their training period,
the magic knights have learned the Heart Kingdom's monomethy
and are growing steadily.
Since Asta has no magic,
he sparred with Gaja, seeking insights that might lead to a new technique.
Meanwhile, in the Clover Kingdom,
Yami finally learned the trick to using monosome.
And now...
Gaja!
Guess who's back for more!
Very impressive.
It seems you've grown quite a bit these past few days.
Yeah!
Yesterday, I had a scrap with the Wind Spirit Guardian,
he helped me train my key,
so I'm way better at reading sneaky attacks now.
And today, I fought the Earth Spirit Guardian,
and she has super sharp senses,
and she helped me hone my fighting instincts like WABAM!
Wait, I thought you were supposed to be training with luck.
He's taking some time to see what he can learn from the other Spirit Guardians,
so it's just me.
I came at the right time then!
Spar with me, I want to try out what I've learned!
I'm perfectly willing to fight more.
But before we start, let's talk a bit.
Even by Arcane Stage standards,
a mage who has no magic is quite the anomaly.
What's even stranger about you is the astounding rate at which you've grown.
So that I might aid you on your quest for even greater strength,
I'd like to ask you some questions.
Please tell me about your life up until this point,
and share whatever you know about the Devil in your grimoire.
Okay then, this might take a while.
It's empty, all right.
Your dreams kes out clockwise.
messy, you've gotta be movies outside!
I won't see there anymore kamu's beenzzle!
Let's ask you some people out live.
It's the same thing!
Sometimes we lose one...
It's their worst desire!
So!
So
You should earn like a diamond
I lived with my beloved sister Lily, Yuno, and all the other orphaned kids
Back then my biggest problem was that I couldn't use any magic at all while Yuno's got so much of the stuff
He does laundry with it. That's right. I'm gonna get the most awesome grimoire ever
I'll join up with the magic knights and once I make a name for myself. I'll follow in your footsteps and become the wizard king
Each March kids turning 15 gather from all over the kingdom to be given grimoires and Yuno and I were finally old enough to receive our own
But hey, uh
Is my grimoire running late or something?
Uh
Try again next year
What?!
Oh wow, you're kidding!
That's actually kind of awesome
Yuno ended up getting a four leaf grimoire just like the first wizard king had
I was so sure all this time. I just needed a grimoire and then I'd finally be able to use magic
And now to not even get a grimoire
No, I won't give up that easily
You're not winning this round fate
Don't underestimate me
It doesn't matter if it takes a year or two or ten or a hundred. I don't care. I'll work till I get that grimoire
But then this thieving jerk showed up out of nowhere and attacked Yuno with his chain magic
He stole Yuno's grimoire and was planning to sell it
Oh, I bet that pendant would fetch a good price. Don't mind if I do
Hold it!
I
I fought hard to get Yuno's grimoire back, but despite all my training I was no match for the thief's magic
He taunted me for my helplessness
Saying that his chains could measure anyone's magic power and that I didn't have a single drop
This world has no use for someone like you a poor magicless fool
You might as well give it all up right now. You were born a loser you worthless runt
Yeah, he's right
No matter how hard I try
I guess there are some things that just aren't possible
So I might as well give
Hey
Who are you calling a loser?
Asta
It's true that you aren't going to become the wizard king
Not ever
You hear that?
Even your little friend knows that it's impossible
That's because I am going to be the wizard king
What?
You're wrong about Asta, Revchi
Very wrong
Asta's no loser. He's my rival
Huh? This is who you would claim as your rival? The only person in the world without magic?
You
Get off of me
Sorry you had to see me at such a weak moment, you know
Just give me a second
That's all then I'll destroy this guy
And then right when I needed it the five leaf grimoire said to have a devil inside it appeared in front of me
Back then I didn't know anything about the devil's powers or the anti-magic that I was about to use
I was offered a sword and I took it
So yeah, that's more or less the whole story of how I came to be the wielder of this grimoire
Hmm
After that me and yuno left we took the magic knights entrance exam at the capital
Yuno ended up joining the most powerful and popular squad the golden dawn
I was almost sent home since I had no magic to speak of but then captain yami let me join the black bulls
If i'm remembering correctly the captain of the black bulls fights with a sword just like you
Yeah, he takes a crazy long time to poop, but he still manages to be there for us when we need him
He's really strong and it's thanks to him that I can use my key
The point is that he's someone I have a whole lot of respect for
Once the rest of the black bulls accepted me as a part of the squad
I got my cape and embarked on my first official mission
That took me and my squad mates to the dungeon where I found my second weapon the demon dweller sword
We also faced off with one of the diamond kingdoms eight shining generals mars
This guy was an insanely strong mage who had two different magical attributes
It was during that battle that I realized
I may not have any magic power, but what I do have are my friends
I borrowed mana from noel and released it using the demon dweller sword and that was enough to break through mars's diamond armor
Afterwards when we reported back on the mission we met the wizard king
Get results a noble heart alone can't protect anyone and the trust of the people is earned not granted
With the wizard king's words in my heart
I protected whoever I could and I beat lots of bad guys
But then I met a bad guy like no other
I haven't introduced myself yet, have I?
I am the leader of the eye of the midnight sun call me licht
His light magic was insanely fast
It was able to hit me before I could react or even see it coming
But thankfully captain yami showed up to save me
He faced licht head on batting his light magic away like it was nothing
I always knew yami was strong, but watching him fight licht proved it in a whole new way
Hey kid were you watching?
Yes, captain. That's good because now it's your turn. Yes, sir
Wait, what are you saying? There's no way I can do that
Yeah, last I checked. I was still your captain
Which means if I tell you to do something you do it
Assuming you want to be a real man someday shrimp stuff
Captain yami told me that he wasn't just reacting to licht's attacks. He was predicting them by sensing licht's key
A person's glance their breathing
Their scent the way their muscles move the hint of their presence taken together all of that living energy people give off
That's called key. All i've been doing is reading his key and using it to predict his moves
You've never done anything like that before
Actually, yeah
The captain's lesson was so intense that I could have died in the middle of it, but in the end I learned how to sense key
How interesting this key sensing technique seems to be well suited to a warrior who lacks magic such as yourself
Your captain yami must have anticipated that such a tool would prove useful as you improve your anti-magic
Come to think of it. Yeah, you're probably right. Oh, holy crap
Captain yami's so freaking cool. Oh, it's possible. I'm simply overthinking this by the way. There's another question. I'd like to ask you
It's a simple one. What do you have to do to enter that special fighting state where the power of your devil manifest in your body?
funny story
The first time I took on that form was in the forest of witches after visiting the queen who rules there
I was fighting this smirky creep from the diamond kingdom who would attack the forest
My magic is never giving up
I'm going up
Damn you it can't be my magic should have made me invincible
To be honest, I didn't understand what was happening any better than the guy I was fighting did
No, no, no, no, no
It's not fair. I stepped on so many people and get where I am now
I can't lose to you
You always kicked your friends down
But my friends helped me be better
stronger
I
Didn't figure out how to take that form at will till I was at Yultim volcano a strong magic region we went to for a training camp
Since I couldn't use mana skin a technique where you protect your body by wrapping it in mana
I was stopped in my tracks by the super intense heat
But then I realized something I could use the key technique
I had learned from captain yami to amplify the anti-magic inside my body and create an anti-magic version of mana skin that worked just as well
And with that same method I can enter that heightened state of being anytime I want to
I'm a lucky guy
Captain yami's done so much for me
I don't know what I would have done if he'd never tell me how to use my key for real
Check out this sword the demon destroyer sword
It's a pretty wild one, but thanks to my key. I can handle it
I hear that sword goes beyond nullifying magic itself
It can also reverse the effects of a spell such a power has great potential
Yep
I got the demon destroyer sword around the time we launched our attack on the eye of the midnight sun's base
This was just before our final battle with them
Things were going well, but then that disloyal guy fully reincarnated and attacked us along with some of our newly possessed friends
Not long after that we ended up fighting the leader of the elves in the center of their base
His key
That sword's got massive power
Uh-oh
I can't stay in this form much longer
Come on, just a little more
Asta
Careful, all right?
Yeah
I know that
Asta!
It turned out that the leader of the elves was the original owner of my swords
So he was able to use their full power
On top of that he was insanely strong
But
I'm not done yet
You're not killing Yuno!
For us to either
He's my rival!
Even with Yuno, I couldn't win
But when I least expected it, the demon destroyer sword I had picked up became a part of my grimoire
Thanks to that
I was able to nullify the poison magic that was used on the people of Hajj village
And return everyone who had been reincarnated into elves back to normal
Afterwards, in the shadow palace
The memories that the demon destroyer had absorbed flooded into me
That's when I found out about the massacre of the elves
And not long after I learned that all the chaos, violence, and hatred I had just witnessed
At a single source
It all began with a devil
You learned soul magic
For us to be never dying
His goal was to leave the world the devil's come from and appear in ours in his full form
With nothing to hold him back
I couldn't let that bastard have his way
I had to stop him
If Yuno could evolve
Then so could I
Anti-magic demon slayer sword!
Blastivider!
Dark cloaked!
Dimension slashed!
Equinox!
Nero used your sealing magic to lock away the damage I had taken
Asta!
Remember
You're going to be
The Wizard King!
Yeah
Right here
Right now
I'm going to push back my limit!
I'm pretty sure you know the rest
I was put on trial for cooperating with the devil but they set me free in the end
I came here to the Heart Kingdom to investigate a devil's curse hoping it would help me prove my innocence back home
Then I found out that the devil's curse in the Heart Kingdom is on Queen Laura Petchka herself
I will get stronger because that's my only path forward
I'll protect all the people I can back home and here in the Heart Kingdom too
I'm glad that you allowed me to hear your tale
It was truly enlightening
I finally understand how you became so powerful despite the fact that you're utterly spurned by mana
Now let us begin
The sun will be setting shortly but we can spar nonetheless
I'll train you as long as you'd like in the dark if need be
Ooh
Right
You wait
It's amazing
You
Now I'm lost
I want to be
Excellent. Noelle, that was a sight to behold.
You put on quite the show.
I think anyone could see that you've improved since you first arrived here.
Well, since I'm royalty myself, I'm a fairly quick study.
I can't believe it! She actually praised me!
In truth, you're the one who's amazing, Water Spirit Andine.
You keep finding new ways to draw out more and more of my water magic.
Thank you for the compliment, but you aren't the only one who's growing fast.
Take a look at this.
It's not just you and Nero.
Your comrades from the Clover Kingdom are learning Heart Kingdom techniques faster than we ever could have imagined.
They're all getting stronger just as fast as you are.
We may be fast, but we still aren't as strong as we need to be to defeat the Devil and the Spade Kingdom.
Right?
Yes, you're exactly right.
That said, I have complete faith in each of you.
The Magic Knights who were training so diligently here,
and your comrades who stayed behind to help prepare the Clover Kingdom for war.
If we all work together, then in time a ray of hope will break through the Spade Kingdom Devil's Cloud of Despair.
In fact, I'm certain that we'll win.
And when we do, I'll avenge my mother.
You shouldn't expect the same trick to work twice.
That move is strong, but as it is now, you can only land a hit with it reliably if you catch your opponent by surprise.
Scenes will finish before dark.
Lightning magic.
Tengiolia.
Not yet!
The leaves of a Clover are set to each contain one thing.
In the first three dwell integrity, hope, and love.
The fourth thing is given over to good luck.
And in the fifth...
There lives a Devil.
Wait, my sword...
What the...
Your capacity for growth continues to surprise me.
In order to reveal the extent of your hidden powers,
I'll attack you with everything I have.
That is, if you think you can withstand more.
Yeah, give me everything you've got!
Things are starting to get interesting now.
Ha ha ha.
No, my way.
Haleに転んで傷ついて気づけば誰ももうどこにもいない
歪んだ世界に魔法の言葉で光が射すなら飛びつくんだろう
今目の前に残るのは希望か
掴みかけた若かな幸福か
まだ消せない誓い叫んでる
忘れないように叫んでる
泣きたいほど遠くだって
全然届かなくても
信じる君は赤いで前を向いている
だから枯れないように抗って
描いた夢また歩き出せる
きっと
僕を
呼ぶ声だ
僕が家のペイ支配近
ご視聴いただきありがとうございました
Clover Kingdom, and everyone in the Heart Kingdom too!